A city of monsters, home to a
slime that bested the Orc Lord...
（ベルヤード）魔物の町と
そこに住む
オークロードをしのぐスライム
（ベルヤード）これは本当なのか？
Can this be true?
いや 本当なのは分かるが…
信じられぬな
No, I know it's true.
I simply can't believe it.
But I have to believe it.
だが 信じるしかないな
我々は そのリムルという名の
スライムに救われたのだと
This slime called Rimuru has saved us.
（フューズ）そうだな
True.
彼らとの関係を
今後 どのようにすべきなのか？
What sort of relationship
should we seek with them?
そのスライムが善意の存在であると
見なして接するか…
And should we do so on the assumption
that this slime is benevolent,
or should we perceive him as a threat
and attempt to eliminate him?
脅威として排除を試みるか…
You speak of eliminating him so
easily, but is it even possible?
排除と簡単に言うが
それは そもそも可能なのかね？
正直に答えていいのか？
Shall I give you an honest answer?
答えを聞くまでもないな
I don't even need to hear it.
（フューズ）フウ…
I suppose we should go and meet him once.
一度 会いに行ってみるか
俺が この目で
I will judge this Rimuru
with my own two eyes.
リムルとやらを
見極めてみるさ
All right, let's move out.
（フューズ）よし 出発するぞ
We're going to go see
this slime you three met.
お前たちが会ったというスライムに
会いにな
（３人）ハア…
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 17: The Gathering
（ミリム）
フウ〜 フウ〜
This is delicious!
うまいのだ！
I love all the food in this town!
この町の食べ物
ぜ〜んぶ好きなのだ
Give me more!
おかわりなのだ！
Were you okay yesterday?
（リムル）昨日は大丈夫だったか？
Nothing to worry about! I—
（ガビル）問題ありませんぞ
我が輩は… ゴホッ
...am quite tough, you know!
頑丈さには自信がありますゆえ
（部下）
さすがガビル様
かっけ〜！
That's Sir Gabiru for you! So cool!
Did your communication crystal work okay?
（リムル）
連絡用の水晶は
うまく作動したか？
（ベスター）
はい ガゼル王へ連絡がつきました
Yes. I was able to contact King Gazel.
I informed him that the Demon Lord Milim
attacked and you dealt with her.
魔王ミリムが来襲し リムル様が
対応したと伝えてあります
Good!
（リムル）
よし ミリムの件は
しばらく様子を見るとして…
We'll just see how things
go with Milim for now.
Be sure to give me a report.
では 報告を頼む
Of course.
This is Great Rimuru's healing potion.
これはリムル様の回復薬です
99% of its composition is
extracted from hipokute herbs.
ヒポクテ草を99パーセント
抽出したものであります
Extracting...
Extraction
You can drink it or apply it on a wound!
飲んで良し ふりかけて良しの
優れもの
完全回復薬 フルポーションです！
The potion of total recovery: full potion!
それに対し ドワーフの技術では
98パーセントの抽出が限界です
In contrast, Dwarven techniques
can only extract up to 98%.
The potions we can make are "high potions."
作れるのは
上位回復薬ハイポーション
A mere 1% makes a tremendous
difference in potency.
たった１パーセント それが
性能の大きな違いとなるのです
And now, at last,
I've overcome that 1% barrier!
そして ついに
その１パーセントの壁を
乗り越えました
This is the result of my research!
これが私の研究成果です！
Oh? All right, I'll appraise it.
（リムル）
ほう… では 鑑定してみるぞ
Please do.
（ベスター）お願いします
Great Sage, use Appraisal.
（リムル）
大賢者(だいけんじゃ)　解析 鑑定だ
Answer.
（大賢者）
解(かい)…
This potion is equal to a full potion.
この薬は
フルポーションに該当します
Well done, Vesta!
It's definitely a full potion!
（リムル）
やったな ベスター
間違いなく フルポーションだぞ！
Excellent work, Vesta!
見事ですな ベスター殿！
Assisting you in this endeavor
was truly worthwhile!
我が輩も
協力したかいがありましたぞ！
Way to go, Vesta!
（カイジン）さすがだな ベスター
I knew you were the right man
for this kind of research!
こういう研究は
やはり お前が適任だと思ってたぜ
ありがとう… ありがとう
Thank you... Thank you.
Wow, I really didn't think
he'd be able to make it.
（リムル）
いや〜
本当に作れるとは思わなかったな
量産に進むとして…
Now, if we move forward
with mass production...
I think if we sold this,
（リムル）この回復薬を売ったら
it'd be a great source of funds
for Tempest. What do you say?
テンペストの資金源となりそうだが
どうだ？
I don't think that's gonna be easy.
旦那 難しいぜ
この薬は性能が良すぎるんだよ
This potion is too effective.
ふだんから気軽に使用できない
We can't rely on it for everyday use.
それこそ英雄級の者たちが
Fine quality like this
is best reserved for high-level champions
in life-or-death situations.
万が一に備えるレベルの
品質だからな
そうですね
That's true.
The potions sold in the
Dwarven Kingdom are low potions,
ドワーフ王国で市販している薬は
ハイポーションを薄めて量産した
ローポーションなのですよ
which are mass-produced
by diluting high potions.
What do you say to
negotiating with King Gazel
ガゼル王と交渉し
ローポーションの生産を
to have those low potions
produced here in Tempest?
テンペストで
請け負ってはいかがですか？
Hey, that could work!
それは ありだな 旦那
If we produce and sell the potions here,
この国で薬の生産をしつつ
販売元になるなら
the Dwarven Kingdom would only need
to procure the necessary ingredients.
ドワーフ王国は
必要量を仕入れるだけで済む
I get it. That would
benefit both nations, huh?
（リムル）
なるほど
それは どちらにも好都合だな
Okay. Let's bring that up for negotiation.
よし 話を詰めることにしよう
You guys can continue
with the production here.
ベスターたちは
引き続き 製造に励んでくれ
Yes, sir!
（リムル）何がどうなっている？
What's going on?
A new guest arrived in town,
（ソウエイ）
新たな客がやってまいりまして
and Lady Milim took exception to him.
その客に対して
ミリム様が激怒し…
（ざわめき）
（リムル）通してくれ
Let me through.
Rigurd, are you okay?
（リムル）リグルド 大丈夫か？
G-Great Rimuru, it's you!
（リグルド）こ… これはリムル様
（リムル）えっ！
Huh?!
（リグルド）
この程度
どうということもございません
This is no cause for concern at all!
No way! That's serious!
（リムル）
いや 大ケガだろ！
This is who did that to you?
（リムル）
あいつに やられたのか？
Correct.
（リグルド）さようで
Oh, Rimuru!
（ミリム）おお リムルよ
Yikes.
This guy thought he could mock us,
so I taught him a lesson!
（ミリム）
こやつが
ナメたマネをしおったから
私が お仕置きしておいたのだ！
I am one of Demon Lord
Carrion's Three Beastketeers,
（フォビオ）
俺は 魔王カリオン様の三獣士(さんじゅうし)
Phobio the Black Leopard Fang.
“黒豹牙(こくひょうが)”フォビオだ
I am the strongest warrior of
the Beast King's Beastketeers.
獣王獣士団(じゅうおうじゅうしだん)の中でも最強の戦士よ
ここは いい町だな
獣王様が支配するにふさわしい
Nice town you've got here.
Fit to be ruled by the Beast King,
don't you think?
そうは思わんか？
ご冗談を…
Surely you jest—
ぐおお！
（ミリム）ぬうう…
なっ… 魔王ミリム？
The Demon Lord Milim?!
くっ… 豹牙爆炎掌(ひょうがばくえんしょう)！
Leopard Fang Flaming Palm!
マブダチの子分に何するのだ〜！
What do you think you're doing
to my bestie's subordinate?!
（リムル）
褒めてほしそうだな
I think she expects me to praise her.
And, um...
う〜んと これは…
Should I really be praising her for this?
褒めていい状況なのか？
I doubt she'll get away with doing this to
an underling of this Demon Lord Carrion.
カリオンとかいう魔王の部下に
手を出してしまった以上
ただじゃ済まないだろうし…
ハア…
Didn't you promise not to cause any
commotion without my permission?
俺の許可なく暴れないと
約束していなかったか？
Huh?!
Er, well...
えっと それは…
Y-Yeah! This is different!
そ… そう！　これは違うのだ
He's not from this town, so it doesn't count!
この町の者ではないから セーフ！
セーフなのだ
It does count.
（リムル）アウトだよ
（ミリム）ええっ！
Huh?!
But since you did stand up for Rigurd,
だが 今回は リグルドを
かばってくれたということで
I'll just make you go without lunch today.
昼メシ抜きで許してやるか
ひどい…
That's cruel... That's too cruel!
ひどいのだ〜！
クソ！
これも全て こいつが悪いのだ
この不届き者！
This is all his fault!
This scumbag!
One hit wasn't enough!
At least give me one more—
１発だけでは飽き足らぬ
（ミリム）せめて もう１発…
（リムル）待て待て 待て！
Wait! Wait! Wait!
はむっ
So, why did you come here?
（リムル）で 何をしに来たんだ？
フンッ 下等なスライム風情に
この俺が答えるとでも？
Hmph. You expect me to answer a lowly slime?
You may call me "lowly,"
but I'm stronger than you.
（リムル）
下等と言うが
お前よりは俺のほうが強いぞ
I don't know this Demon Lord Carrion.
俺は
魔王カリオンとやらを知らないし
Depending on how you behave, my people
could become Carrion's enemies.
お前の態度しだいで カリオンは
俺たちと敵対することになるんだぞ
Do you want to be solely responsible for
antagonizing the entire Great Forest of Jura?
お前の一存で
このジュラの大森林全てを
敵に回すつもりなのか？
ハン！　偉そうに
Hah! That's big talk.
This whole town is loyal to
a lowly monster like you?
この町は
こんな下等な魔物に従うのか？
雑魚ばかりだと大変だな
Must be rough having nothing
but weaklings around.
Don't get a big head just because
Lady Milim took a liking to you.
ミリム様に気に入られているからと
調子に乗るなよ
おい お前
Hey! Are you talking trash about my friend?
私の友達に
ナメた口をきくじゃないか
Milim, stop. If you do anything else,
you can kiss dinner goodbye.
（リムル）ミリム 待て
お前 今度 何かしたら
マジで晩メシを抜くからな？
Okay. I'll be quiet.
分かった おとなしくするのだ
Now, it's true that I'm a slime.
（リムル）
さて 俺は確かにスライムだ
But it's also a fact that
I rule 30% of this forest,
だが 俺が この森の３割を
支配しているのは本当だし
and if you're really serious, we may
have no choice but to declare war.
そちらがその気なら 戦争するのも
やむをえないと思っている
So think carefully before you answer me.
なので
よく考えて返事をすることだ
Lord Carrion ordered me to come here and
scout some mysterious majin to serve him.
謎の魔人たちを
配下へとスカウトするように
カリオン様より命じられて
やって来たんだ
Oh? He must mean us.
（リムル）ほう 俺たちのことだな
Looks like Milim wasn't the only
Demon Lord who had an eye on that battle.
（リムル）
どうやら ミリムと同じく
ほかの魔王たちも
俺たちの戦いを見ていたらしいな
Damn that Carrion! He broke his promise!
（ミリム）
カリオンのヤツ
約束を破りおって…
Well, I get the picture.
まっ 話は分かった
じゃあ 帰っていいぞ
You can leave now.
（フォビオ）え？
（ベニマル）リムル様？
Huh?
Great Rimuru...
Are you sure about this?
（シオン）よろしいのですか？
Well, I can't kill him, can I?
（リムル）
だって 殺すわけにはいかないだろ
Tell the Demon Lord Carrion
魔王カリオンに伝えろ
that if he wants to talk, he can
choose a date and contact us again.
俺たちと交渉したいなら
日時を改めて連絡をよこすようにと
きっと後悔させてやる
I'll make you regret this.
Doesn't look like he'll
relay any message for us...
（リムル）
あの様子じゃあ
伝言は無理っぽいな
Okay, I want to know all about
this Demon Lord Carrion.
さて
魔王カリオンについて話が聞きたい
I can't tell you that.
それはリムルにも教えられないぞ
We've sworn not to interfere with each other.
お互い邪魔をしないという
約束なのだ
And there it is! She just confessed
that there's some secret!
（リムル）
はい
秘密があると自白を頂きました！
Did you only make that promise with Carrion?
それはカリオンだけとの約束か？
Or does it involve other Demon Lords, too?
それとも
ほかの魔王も関係しているのかな？
Uh, that's...
あっ いや それは…
Hey, it's okay!
大丈夫だって
Carrion used his underling to
interfere with you, didn't he?
カリオンってヤツだって
部下を使って
邪魔してきたんだろ？
And we're besties, so we
help each other out, right?
俺たちは
マブダチなんだから
お互いに
助け合うじゃん？
So I think it'd be a good idea for me
to know about the other Demon Lords.
だったら 俺も
ミリム以外の
魔王のことを
知っておいたほうが
いいと思うんだよね
If I don't know what kind
of promise you made,
ミリムが どんな約束をしたか
知っておかないと
I might end up interfering
without realizing it.
俺が知らずに
邪魔しちゃうかもしれないしさ
That's true...
確かに
But... Besties...
でも マブダチ…
I know!
（リムル）そうだ！
今度 俺が武器を作ってやるよ
I'll make a weapon for you!
I'm concerned for you as
your bestie, after all!
やっぱ マブダチとしては
ミリムが心配だしさ！
A new weapon?!
新しい武器…
アハハハ そうだな！
Yeah, that's right!
Nothing's more important than your bestie!
やはり マブダチは
いちばん大事なのだ〜！
Too easy. She's way too easy.
（リムル）
チョロい
あまりにもチョロすぎる
Demon Lords Clayman, Carrion, Frey,
（リムル）
魔王クレイマン カリオン フレイ
and you, Milim, used Gelmud in a
scheme to create a puppet Demon Lord.
そして ミリムが
ゲルミュッドを使って
傀儡(くぐつ)となる魔王の誕生を
もくろんだと
It was just a way to kill time.
単なる退屈しのぎだったのだ
Maybe that's all it was to you,
（リムル）
ミリムにとっては
そうかもしれないが…
but since we butted in, I guess it's
inevitable that they'd target us.
それを邪魔した以上
俺たちが狙われるのは当然か
It seems likely that other Demon
Lords will become involved, as well.
これは ほかの魔王たちも
絡んでくるでしょうね
What a predicament...
なんということ…
トレイニー様にも相談せねば
We must consult with Lady Treyni.
It'll be fine!
大丈夫です
Great Rimuru has nothing to fear
from any of those Demon Lords!
リムル様ならば ほかの魔王など
恐るるに足りません
Well, I've told you the secret.
ということで 秘密は話したのだ
Now give me my new weapon,
like you promised, bestie!
約束どおり新しい武器をよこすのだ
マブダチ！
ワ〜ッハハハ！
The storm that arose along
with Demon Lord Milim's attack
（リムル）
魔王ミリムの来襲とともに
巻き起こった暴風は
would gain strength along its path
より勢いを増しつつ
リムルたちの国を
to swallowing up Rimuru's
nation and his people.
のみ込んでいくことに
なるのだった
One of the nations surrounding the Great
Forest of Jura, the Kingdom of Falmuth,
（リムル）
ジュラの大森林
その周辺の国のひとつ
ファルムス王国は
Barren Lands
The Western Provinces
The Eastern Plains
Tempest
is a major trade power known as the
gateway to the Western Provinces.
西側諸国の玄関口と呼ばれる
商業の大国である
Kingdom of Ingrassia
Kingdom of Shiltrozzo
Kingdom of Falmuth
Kingdom of Blumund
Armed Nation
of Dwargon
Canaat Mountains
Sealed Cave
Lake Siss
It was from this kingdom
この国からジュラの森へ
that a team was sent to the Forest
of Jura to learn about the Orc Lord.
オークロード調査団が
向けられていた
Led by a man named Youm,
ヨウムという男をリーダーとした
they're a rowdy gang,
brought together by money.
金でかき集められた
荒くれ者の集団である
Captain of the Border Survey Corps  Youm
Boss—
（カジル）カシラ…
（ヨウム）しっ！
Shh.
（ギド）ちょ… ヤバいでやす！
Whoa, this is bad!
（エレン）でもでも〜！
（カバル）おい お前ら…
But, but...
You guys... Whoa! Watch it!
（カバル）って うお 危ねえ！
Farsight
（フューズ）
こんなデタラメで今まで
よく生き延びてたな
How have you three stayed alive
so long by being this careless?!
貴様ら！
Sounds like some people
have encountered a monster.
（ヨウム）
魔物と遭遇した人間がいるようだ
What should we do, boss?
（カジル）カシラ どうしやす？
（エレン）わああ〜！
Hey! Wait for us!
（ギド）
ちょ… あねさん！
待つでやすよ！
Sorry to butt in!
（エレン）お邪魔します〜
We appreciate the help!
（カバル）お世話になります
Sorry about this!
（ギド）すいやせんね
Here it comes!
（ヨウム）来るぞ
（ロンメル）ええっ！
（カジル）ナイトスパイダー？
A Knight Spider?!
All right, boys, assume formation.
よ〜し お前ら 陣形を組め
負傷者は すぐに下がらせて回復
Remove and heal anyone who gets hurt.
This is an order! Everyone stay alive!
命令だ　全員 生き残れ！
（一同）おう！
Yeah!
Kajir, take command.
カジル 指揮を執れ
Got it.
分かった
Rommel, use a strengthening spell on me.
（ヨウム）
ロンメル 俺に強化魔法を
てめえら…
And you guys...
I'll make you pay for getting
us involved in this later.
俺たちを巻き込んだ落とし前
あとで
きっちりつけてもらうからな
Hey, Kaval! Is that you?
（ゴブタ）
あれ？
カバルさんじゃないっすか？
Good to see you again!
（ゴブタ）お久しぶりっす
Gobta!
（カバル）ゴブタ君！
（ヨウム）あ…
You're fighting monsters
every time I see you.
毎回 魔物と戦ってるようっすけど
Do you enjoy fighting that much?
そんなに戦うのが好きなんすか？
But I'll handle this one.
でも ここは おいらが…
今日の晩ご飯っす〜！
You're for dinner today!
ウソだろ…
You're kidding me...
こいつ
めちゃめちゃ おいしいんすよ〜
These things are seriously
delicious, you know!
It'll be ready soon!
もうすぐ煮えるっすよ〜
I can't wait!
待ちきれないのだ！
I'm the representative of
this town... or nation...
（リムル）
俺が この町というか国というか
called the Jura Tempest Federation.
My name's Rimuru Tempest.
ジュラ･テンペスト連邦国の
代表をしている
リムル＝テンペストだ
You really are a slime!
本当に スライムが…
By the way, Rimuru, there are some
folks here we didn't see last time.
（カバル）ところで リムルの旦那
以前には見かけなかった方が
おられるようですが
Oh, yeah. This is Benimaru,
Shion, Souei, and Shuna.
（リムル）ああ ベニマルにシオン
ソウエイ シュナ
And that's Milim.
それと ミリムだ
So, the Kingdoms of Blumund and Falmuth
have both come to investigate this place?
（リムル）
で ブルムンド王国と
ファルムス王国から
それぞれ ここの調査に来たと
We are—
（フューズ）我々は…
（ヨウム）ていうか
Wait a minute.
Why is a slime acting like such a bigshot?
なんでスライムが
そんなに偉そうにしてるんだよ？
It makes no sense!
おかしいだろ
何なんだ 一体？
なんで お前らは納得してるんだ？
What's the deal here?
Why are all of you okay with this?
（シオン）リムル様に無礼ですよ
（ヨウム）うるさい
You are insulting Great Rimuru.
Shut your mouth, Tits!
（ヨウム）黙ってろ おっぱい！
（リムル）わあ！
（ロンメル）ヨウム〜！
（カジル）カシラ！
Boss!
Youm!
H-Hey...
（リムル）おっ おい…
I'm sorry!
（シオン）あ… つい！
Sorry about what Shion did.
（リムル）
うちのシオンが すまんな
She has trouble restraining
herself sometimes.
ちょっと我慢が
足りないところがあるんだ
Cut her some slack.
許してやってほしい
That's mean! I'm actually
known for my patience!
（シオン）ひどいです
これでも
忍耐力には定評があるのですよ？
You've got a long way to go if
you're that impatient, Shion!
我慢が足りぬとは まだまだだな
シオン
You're so short-tempered because you
don't have an open mind like I do.
私のように心を広く持たぬから
そんな短気なのだぞ
I want to be on good terms with Humans.
（リムル）
俺は
人間とも仲良くしたいと考えている
I hope we can trade and network
with you all someday, too.
そのうち貿易とかして
交流できればいいなと思ってるしさ
Trade?
（フューズ）貿易？
（リムル）ああ
Yeah.
We've actually entered diplomatic relations
with the Dwarven Kingdom already.
（リムル）
実は ドワーフ王国とも
国交を開いている
With Dwargon?!
ドワルゴンと？
I think passing through this land would
be more convenient for your merchants.
（リムル）この地を経由すれば
商人たちの利便性も
向上すると思うけど どうかな？
What do you think?
Now, wait a minute!
いや 待ってください
You're saying that Dwargon acknowledges
this nation of monsters as legitimate?
ドワルゴンが この魔物の国を
承認したというのですか？
（ベスター）
その話 私が保証します
I can vouch for that.
Minister Vesta!
（フューズ）ベスター大臣！
Former minister.
元… 大臣です
What is a man of your standing doing here?
あなたほどの人物が
どうして ここに…
It's good to see you again, Fuze.
（ベスター）
お久しぶりです フューズ殿
What Great Rimuru says is true.
リムル様のおっしゃっていることは
本当です
King Gazel and Rimuru have
entered into a treaty.
ガゼル王とリムル様は
盟約を交わしておられます
Are you convinced now?
（リムル）納得してくれたかな？
W-Well... If that is the case, we aren't
opposed to cooperating with you.
（フューズ）
はっ はあ… そういうことでしたら
我々としても
協力は やぶさかではありません
But I'll need to see undeniable proof
that you are, in fact, an ally of Humans.
ただし あなたが本当に
人間の味方なのかどうか
しっかりと
確かめさせてもらうことにしますが
かまいませんね？
I assume that's all right?
Oh, sure. That's to be expected.
（リムル）
ん？　ああ それは当然だろう
それでかまわないよ
I'm just fine with that.
I'll permit you to stay here.
滞在を許可する
I want you to understand
that we aren't a threat.
俺たちが脅威でないと
分かってほしい
By the way, Fuze-san,
ところで フューズさんとやら
has the news that the Orc Lord was
defeated already gotten around?
オークロードが倒された
という情報は
既に知れ渡っているのか？
いや この情報を
知るのは国王と
No, only our king and a select
handful of people know that.
ごく一部の者たちのみ
ですよ
I see. In that case...
（リムル）ほう ならば…
Youm-kun, want to make a contract with me?
ヨウム君 俺と契約しない？
Huh? What are you even talki—
はあ？　一体 何を言って…
What... might you be suggesting?
何を… 言っておられるんですか？
You said the Kingdom of Falmuth
hired you with money, right?
（リムル）
ファルムス王国には
金(かね)で雇われたって言ってたろ？
So you'd just be switching employers.
だったら
雇い主が変わるだけのことだ
To put it in simple terms...
簡単に説明するとだな…
I want you guys to be the champions
who defeated the Orc Lord.
君たちに オークロードを倒した
英雄となってもらいたいのだよ
What?!
Just say that we simply helped you out,
（リムル）
俺たちは ヨウムに協力しただけで
and start a rumor that you were
the one who defeated the Orc Lord.
実際には ヨウムが
オークロードを倒したというふうに
うわさを流してもらえればいい
I figure, that way,
そうすれば 英雄を助けた
信用できる魔物という立ち位置を
I can be known as the trustworthy
monster who assisted the champion.
確立できるのではないかな〜って
I think it'll be easier to
befriend people that way
謎の脅威的な魔物というよりも
than if they think I'm some
mysterious, threatening monster.
そっちのほうが親しみやすい感じに
なると思うんだが どうだろう？
What do you say?
（ベニマル）なるほど…
I get it.
Well put.
（ソウエイ）さすがです
Have you gathered your thoughts?
（リムル）
考えは まとまったかな？
Rimuru... No, Mr. Rimuru.
（ヨウム）リムル… さん
This town is really something.
これは大した町だ
After seeing all of them, I know
you're not some evil being.
あんたが
邪悪な存在じゃないってのは
あいつらを見て よく分かった
We are people of guilty conscience.
俺たちは すねに傷を持つ身だ
We always longed to be free men.
ずっと 自由の身になりたかった
We accepted the mission to come here
今回の任務を受けたのは
途中で自分たちを死んだことにして
because we planned to make everyone
think we'd died on the way
and then head for some safe nation.
どこか安全な国に
向かうつもりだったからだ
I've decided.
決めたぜ
俺は あんたを信用する
I'll trust you.
Allow me to call you
"Master Rimuru" from now on.
今日からは
“リムルの旦那”と呼ばせてもらう
I am at your command.
何なりと命じてほしい
Sure. I'll be counting on you.
（リムル）ああ よろしく頼むよ
Thus, Youm and his companions
began training under Hakurou
（リムル）
こうして ヨウムたちは
ハクロウの下
to look like champions.
英雄に見えるよう
修行を行うことになった
That didn't take long.
（クレイマン）
早かったですね
気付かれませんでしたか？　ティア
You weren't noticed, were you, Tear?
I'm part of the Moderate Harlequin
Alliance, too, you know!
（ティア）
あたいだって
中庸道化連(ちゅうようどうけれん)の一員なんだ
Have a little faith in me!
少しは信用してよね
I'm just concerned you might go overboard.
あなたが むちゃをしないか
私は心配なのです
Jeez! Stop treating me like a child already!
（ティア）
もう！
いつまでも子供扱いは やめてよね
分かりましたよ
Very well.
ミュウランから報告がありました
I received word from Myulan.
It seems Milim has taken quite
a liking to those majin.
魔王ミリムは よほど
あの魔人どもを気に入った様子
Huh...
（ティア）へえ〜
This is turning out to be more
interesting than I expected.
（クレイマン）
これは思った以上に面白い展開です
How truly delightful.
愉快ですよ まったく
Well, that's great,
（ティア）それなら いいけど…
but what's really going on?
実際のとこ どうなの？
Is this majin really so amazing that the
Demon Lord Milim would take interest?
魔王ミリムが興味を持つくらい
すごい魔人なの？
Only to the point that we
mustn't simply ignore it.
無視はできないという程度でした
He was no match for me, after all.
私の敵ではなかったですし
But then again, Laplace...
しかし ラプラスがですね…
What about Laplace?
（ティア）ラプラスが？
Shall we call it... an eeriness?
（クレイマン）
不気味さ… とでもいうのか
He says he felt something of that nature.
何かを感じたと言うんですよ
Oh, really?
（ティア）ふ〜ん そっか
If a cunning guy like Laplace said so,
maybe there really is something!
あの こずるいラプラスが
言ってたんなら
やっぱり なんかあるんじゃない？
At the very least,
少なくとも
魔王ミリムが興味を持った理由は
I think we should find out why the
Demon Lord Milim's taken such an interest.
知るべきだと思うよ
Yes, we certainly will need to gather more
information and give it some thought.
（クレイマン）確かに
もっと情報を集めて
検討しないといけませんね
Yeah, we should!
（ティア）うん それがいいよ
So, as for the results of my investigation!
で！　調査結果だけど…
Let's hear it.
伺いましょう
Well, Frey apparently has no interest in
getting involved with the Forest of Jura.
（ティア）
フレイはね
ジュラの森に関わる気はないみたい
She seemed wary of something.
何かを警戒している様子だった
It was almost as if she
was preparing for battle!
まるで戦争準備でもしている感じ？
やあ やあ！
And did you find out the reason for that?
その原因は分かりましたか？
I did! You won't believe this!
（ティア）
分かったよ！
なんと びっくり！
She was freaking out, saying Charybdis
was going to be revived!
あのカリュブディスが
復活するって慌ててたよ！
Charybdis?
（クレイマン）カリュブディス…
I see.
なるほど
Now, Tear, I have another
task I'd like you to handle.
では ティア
次の仕事を頼みたいのですが
（ティア）
ニヒヒッ そうくると思ってた
I thought you would!
I've already called Footman,
so a little fighting is no problem!
フットマンのヤツも呼んでるから
多少の荒事も大丈夫！
That's wonderful, Tear.
（クレイマン）
さすがですね ティア
But I would like you to avoid
violence as much as possible.
ですが なるべくは暴力はなしで
お願いします
First, seek out the location of the seal
まずは封印の地を探し出し
カリュブディスを
手なずけることができるかどうか
and find out whether or
not we can tame Charybdis.
それを探ってください
Leave it to me, Clayman!
（ティア）任せてよ クレイマン
The location should be—
（クレイマン）場所は恐らく…
（ティア）任せてって言ったでしょ
I said leave it to me!
Okay, I'm going now!
（ティア）
それじゃあ あたいは行くね
Charybdis, eh?
カリュブディス… ですか
With power said to rival
that of the Demon Lords...
魔王に匹敵するといわれる その力
I truly look forward to
seeing what it is like.
どれほどのものか
非常に楽しみですね
Next time, "Evil Creeps Closer."
（大賢者）
次回「忍び寄る悪意」
Evil Creeps Closer